NASIPHI NGCOBOZI

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have done programming and specialised in systems development, in 2016 which was the last year of my degree I was involved in project where we build an online voting system. I have basic background of Web design. I have experience that is more than 2 years in customer service. I have done Microsoft certification. I have done training/ facilitation certificates also have experience on training field.

EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE 10/2022 to 05/2023

Webhelp, Cape Town, South Africa

- Provided primary customer support to internal and external customers
- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward- thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns
- Clarified customer issues and determined root cause of problems to resolve product or service complaints
- Answered customer telephone calls promptly to avoid on-hold wait times.

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE 06/2022 to 09/2022

Vodacom, Cape Town, South Africa

- To monitor, track and coordinate all Technical department functions including tickets, calls, complaints and mail queries from customers.
- Ensure that customers are informed as to the progress of queries logged but not resolved.
- Ensure that the customers are called, and the resolution is confirmed before queries are closed.

FACILATITION / TRAINING 06/2020 to 12/2023

Usapho Loluhle, East London

- Planning and creating the lesson plan
- Task management, motivating learners and managing the emotional culture of the group
- Monitoring and assessing portfolios.

STUDENT 02/2021 to 02/2022

Netcampus, Cape Town, Soth Africa

- · Life or soft skills
- End User Training
- Microsoft Teams MS 100
- Microsoft 365 Fundamentals MS 900
- Windows 10 MD 100
- Modern desktop Technician MD 101
- Service Desk Analysis SDA
- Microsoft Azure Fundamentals AZ 900
- Microsoft Administrator AZ 104

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- C#
- C++
- Java Scrip
- HTML
- PhP
- Life/Soft Skills

- End User Training
- Microsoft Teams MS 700
- Microsoft 365
 Fundamentals
- MS 900
- Windows 10 MD 100
- Modern Desktop

- Technician MD 101
- SDA Service Desk Analyst
- Microsoft Azure
- Fundamentals AZ 900
- Administrator AZ 104

EDUCATION

Nozuko Senior Secondary School

Grade 12, Physical Science, Life Science, Mathematics, Geography, 2012

Richfield Institute of Technology, Durban

BSc IT: BSc, IT, 2017

Modules: Artificial Intelligence 700, Computer Security700, IT Project Management 731, Programming 731, Programming 741, Software Engineering Management 700, Data Warehousing & Data Mining Modules: IT Group Project 732, Programming 732, Programming 742 Research Methodology 800, Work Integrated Learning 700